Connie Tsang

I'm a front-end developer with a zeal for details, problem-solving, accessibility + user experience. With over a decade running a successful photography business, I bring an aesthetic sensibility, outstanding people skills + the organizational know-how to consistently deliver on time. ...I also get pretty excited about meeting people's pets.

connietsangcodes@gmail.com (416) 826-2910

connietsangcodes.com

Github: connietee22
Linkedin: connietsang

PROJECTS

Gimme Dumplings - jQuery, HTML, CSS

Juno Grad Directory - React, HTML, CSS, Firebase

Reading With Caffeine - React, HTML, CSS, API (Group collaboration)

Dial-A-PeeWee - jQuery, HTML, CSS

Bottom Bin Cinema - jQuery, HTML, CSS (Pair-programming)

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, Toronto — Certificate

APR 2020 - OCT 2020

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp, JavaScript 101, Web Development

Ryerson University, Toronto — Bachelor of Applied Arts

SEP 1995 - MAY 1999

Radio and Television Arts program: final year focus on news research.

EXPERIENCE

Connie Tsang Photography, Toronto — Owner/Photographer

March 2008 - PRESENT

- Managed a freelance business, from photography to administration, increasing revenue and client load on an annual basis.
- Developed and nurtured long-term relationships with TIFF, University of Toronto, Aga Khan Museum, Shantell Martin, Buddies in Bad Times.
- Produced 10+ photo essays, photographing and interviewing subjects from senior square-dancers to an Elvis impersonator.

Toronto International Film Festival, Toronto — *Image Editor*

JUN 2008 - SEP 2019 (ANNUAL SUMMER CONTRACT)

- Promoted to Image Editor of programme book in 2012 after roles as Graphic
 Production Assistant + Programme Book Coordinator
- Managed editing and delivery of images ahead of schedule, juggling needs and deadlines of the printer, design, digital, and conference teams.

VOLUNTEER

Canadian National Institute for the Blind — Virtual Vision Mate

West Neighbourhood House — Visitor, Friendly Connection Program for Seniors and People with Disabilities

Coveted Canines — Foster Dog Parent

National Ballet School — Dance Assistant, Sharing Dance for People with Parkinson's

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SCSS

JavaScript fundamentals, React, jQuery

Photoshop, Lightroom

Responsive design

RESTful APIs & Firebase

Web accessibility

Git and Github

Paired-programming & team development

Project scope management

Excellent interpersonal skills

Reliable, organized, adaptable

Detail- and deadline-oriented

Self-starter with willingness to learn and get to work

Team player w/ a great attitude

HONOURS + AWARDS

Ontario Arts Council

Chalmers' Professional
Development Grant for emerging
artists \$7500

PechaKucha: Tokyo Presenter

Luminato Youth Photography
Program Guest lecturer

Project Kids and CamerasGuest lecturer

Photographers Without Borders: Lima, Peru Photographer